Preliminary Guide to the Office of Records and Benefits records 1954-1992 RG0066
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Office of Records and Benefits records
1954-1992
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
George Washington University. Division of Records and Benefits
RG0066
5.25 Linear Feet
Materials in the collection include personnel, fringe benefits, and policy files from 1954 to 1992.
Restrictions on Access
The contents of Series 3 must be reviewed for restricted employee records prior to use; these records are closed to research for 75 years from date of record creation. Series 3 is closed to research for 75 years from date of record creation.
Acquisition Information
Acquisition data is unknown for this collection.
Historical or Biographical Note
Human Resource Services at The George Washington University is made up of four divisions. These are Benefit Services, Employee Relations, Staffing and Compensation Services and Records and Dat Management. At one point the Records and Benefits office was a part personnel services at the University This note was written in 2005.
Collection Scope and Content
Materials in the collection include personnel, fringe benefits, and policy files from 1954 to 1992.
Fromerly RG 8.6.3
Collection Organization
Organized in three series: General files, Office files, and Personnel files.
Washington (D.C.); Employee fringe benefits; George Washington University
- Office files, 1954-1992; RG0066 Series 1; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents note
  This series consists of correspondence, manuals, brochures, applications, regulations memorandums, forms, a poster, a study, and other files. They range in date from 1954 to 1992. Th materials concern employee benefits; sick and annual leave; affirmative action; dental insurance tuition benefits; regulations governing administrative assistants and research personnel; wage pric and hiring freezes; accident and injury claims; salaries; the Budget Office; the Office of Budgetin and Planning; education benefits; the credit union; the Faculty/Employee Assistance Program; healt care plans, and filling vacancies.
  Formerly vertical files
  - Employee Handbook, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Faculty/Employee Assistance Program, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - GWU Health Plan, 1978 ca.-1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Personnel Services, Department of, 11/25/196 -02/1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Personnel Services, Department of Records and Benefits, 05/01/197 -05/29/1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - University Research - Regulations Governing Administrativ Assistants and Research Personnel, 03/31/195 -06/1961 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Employee Handbook and Employee Assistance Program brochure, 1999; Series 1 (Box SHARED 2, Folder 7)
- General files, 1957-1987; RG0066 Series 2; 7.5 Linear Feet 5 record center cartons (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5)
  This series contains files about fringe benefits as well as the general management of personnel, salaries, and benefits at the university and hospital. The material dates from 1957-87, with the bulk being from around 1979-1987.
  Formerly ACC#184
  This series has a paper container list in the reading room, please ask staff for assistance.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Other Finding Aids
- Personnel records, RG0066 Series 3; 10.5 Linear feet
  This series contains personnel records from employees at GW during World War II. Included are th personal files of workers at the Allegany laboratory. These files contain photographs of workers correspondence, term dates, and other information relating to their positions at the University These materials range in date from 1940-1950.
  - Kenneth Harrington, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Walter J. Harrington, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Henry T. Harris, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Todd Harris, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Harry E. Hart, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Howard S. Hartman, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - William C. Hartsock, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Allen Zimmerman Harvey, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - David C. Haupt, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Lee Haus, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Albert W. Havner, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Charlene D. Hawn, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Robert A. Hayes, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Charlotte Ann Haynie, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Walter O. Heim, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Betty Jane Heishman, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - John Lewis Heller, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Delos Henderson, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - John R. Hendley, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Anna M. Hendrick, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Warren A. Hendricks, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Oliver P. Hendrickson, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Melvin Henry, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Beverly Rose Hershberger, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Eleanor C. Hesse, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Ernest F. Hickle, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Margueritte E. Hickman, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Howard Ernest Higbie, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Adeline J. Higgs, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Joseph Harrison Higgs, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Z. Elizabeth Higgs, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Leona B. High, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Phyllis Marie Hill, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Ralph F. Hilleary, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Loretta Nellie Himmler, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Elizabeth S. Hinds, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Ernest M. Hiner, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Albert N. Hines, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Charles P. Hines, undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Walter E. Hines, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - William A. Hines, undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Mrs. Willie P. Hines, undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Jay C. Hite, undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Luther Kenneth Hite, undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Marcus E. Hobbs, undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Adolph Howell, undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Jerome J. Howland, undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Emory S. Howsare, undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - M. Doris Webster Hoyle, undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Charles A. Hubbard, undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Robert M. Hubbard, undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Bland A. Huey, undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Jacqueline Huff, undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Jobe Huffman, undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Minor Huffman, undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Mary C. Hulings, undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - M. Shirley Humbertson, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Roy E. Hunt, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Richard Hunton, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - John D. Hurley, Jr., undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Carson F. Hyde, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Marl H. Hyde, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Kathleen E. Hymes, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Virgil R. Ice, Jr., undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Elsie R. Idleman, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Ralph C. Isiminger, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Glenn Barclay Isneberg, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Irene S. Ives, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Homer R. Jackson, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - M. Adele Jackson, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Marguerite E. Jackson, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Ward W. Jackson, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Sarah L. Jacobson, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Hans M. Jacobson, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Robert Lee James, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Ward Jamison, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Albert Lee Jenkins, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Alverta L. Jenkins, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Glenn P. Jenkins, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Charles J. Jenkins, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Chester Jenkins, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - George B. Jenkins, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Robert Joel, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Esther L. Johansson, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - John F. Johnson, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Phyllis Lee Johnson, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Vera N. Johnson, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Elizabeth J. Johnston, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Milan Alexander Johnston, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Dorothy M. Jones, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Elmer Jones, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Richard N. Jones, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Roger L. Jones, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Leon H. Judy, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Marnie E. Judy, undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Bernard W. Jung, undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Edward S. Junkins, undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Francis W. Kaefer, undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Beatrice Kartus, undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Thomas Keating, undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Carroll Keebaugh, undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Charles A. Keech, Sr., undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Charlotte J. Keefauver, undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Owen Francis Keegan, Jr., undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Charles W. Keesecker, undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Eugene A. Keewan, undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Beulah M. Keister, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Ruth Elizabeth Keiter, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Claude S. Keller, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Martha S. Keller, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Francis Patrick Kelley, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - John J. Kelley, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Joseph L. Kelley, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Frank Patrick Kelley, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Elizabeth L. Kelso, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - George Edward Kelso, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Evelyn M. Kennedy, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Orville Carl Kennell, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Mary G. Kenney, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Peter T. Kenney, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - John C. Kenney, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Osie C. Kerns, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Charles Francis Kerr, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - M. Amanda Kershner, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Richard B. Kershner, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Alston G. Kesner, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Harlie M. Kesner, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Elmer S. Kight, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Emory L. Kimberlin, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Guy E. Kimble, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - James F. Kincaid, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Charles J. King, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Paul Kingsley, undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Barbara Ways Kirby, undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Byron Harman Kiser, Jr., undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Roscoe L. Kitzmiller, undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Lewis Charles Kleinhans, undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Wallace C. Kline, undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Constance I. Knapp, undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Leona Perdew Knapp, undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Phillip H. Knepp, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Cecil C. Knight, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Eva A. Knippenberg, undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Shelvia M. Koontz, undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Marian Lee Koritz, undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Dr. Alexander I. Kossiakoff, undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Jack Kramer, undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Beverly Brooks Pardy Krause, undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Lewis Lee Kuh, undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Charles H. Kunes, undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Bernie Kurkendal, undated (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Harrison Bradley Kyle, undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Margaret Bernadette La Carte, undated (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Millard H. La Joy, undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Benjamin A. La Neve, undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Mary Jane Lakin, undated (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - John W. Lancaster, undated (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - William J. Lance, undated (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Lt. Comdr. Donald E. Lane, USNR, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Neva L. Lane, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Clyde E. Largent, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Mary Ellen Larsen, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Clyde V. La Rue, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Harland A. Lasher, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Nevin E. Lashley, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Carl M. Lathrop, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Frances L. Lawler, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Charles A. Lawrence, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Elmer J. Lawrence, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Maryland V. Lawrence, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Leslie L. League, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Frank E. Leake, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Howard A. Leap, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Baker B. Lease, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Margaret J. Lease, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Andrew H. Leatherman, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Daniel Leenov, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Wayne L. Lees, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Ora Mae Schell Leith, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - D. Vivian Lehman, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Bert V. Leonard, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Jefferson Leonard, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Jack Levin, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Brady M. Lewis, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Edward D. Lewis, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Elwood F. Lewis, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Harry W. Lewis, undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - June E. Lewis, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Thomas Franklin Lewis, undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Mabel Lightfoot, undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Melvin Liller, undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - George W. Lilly, undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Robert Lindahl, undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Gilbert L. Lindeman, undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Frank W. Lindner, undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Mary Lou Lippold, undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Herbert Lister, undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Stanley Marsh Lister, undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Roy L. Little, undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Vernon A. Livengood, undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - William B. Livingston, undated (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - George T. Loar, undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Helen R. Loewendick, undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - James Lofton, undated (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Robert E. Logsdon, undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Edryn K. Long, undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - William F.E. Long, II, undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Mary Alice Lookenott, undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Aurora Lillian Loss, undated (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Letha Gross Loy, undated (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Clyde Dean Lucas, undated (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Ruth Jeanne Ludolph, undated (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Ray F. Ludwig, undated (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Edna T. Lueck, undated (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Alfred Onno Luning, undated (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - John T. Luzier, undated (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Gordon H. Lyle, undated (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Doris Ellen Lyon, undated (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Ervin Mace, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Dorothea Elizabeth Madaire, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Arthur J. Madden, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Joseph A. Madero, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Sally Ann Maginnis, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - George H. Malaney, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - David R. Malcolm, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - William Malcolm, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - James G. Maley, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Edward F. Malloy, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Mary Elizabeth Malloy, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Charles H. Malone, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Jacob Malone, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Leonora P. Malone, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Roy A. Malone, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - William F. Malone, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Katharine C. Mann, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Nelson Samuel Marans, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Muriel A. Marcosano, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - John F. Markley, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Helen V. Markwood, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Albert Martin, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Carl R. Martin, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Lamar T. Martin, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Rita Ann Martin, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - John E. Martz, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Elizabeth F. Massie, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Mary Smeltz Mathews, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Betty L. Matthew, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Agnes M. Mattingly, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Agnes M. Mattingly, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Robert E. Meager, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - David D. Mease, undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Mrs. Lorraine Messersmith, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Olive Ann Metz, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - James H. Meyers, undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Perry Lee Michael, undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Betty Michelson, undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - William Lloyd Mickey, undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Ruth S. Mierley, undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Helen Juanita Milby, undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Chester Miller, undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Frank N. Miller Jr., undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Gordon Blake Miller, undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Leo Clifton Miller, undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Leo W. Miller, undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - LeRoy E. Miller, undated (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Jackson T. Mills, undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - William A.D. Millson, undated (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Philip M. Minke, undated (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - John Joseph Moakley, undated (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Agnes G. Mock, undated (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Thomas P. Monahan, undated (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence and Order Slips-A, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence and Order Slips-B, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence and Order Slips-C [1/2], undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence and Order Slips-C [2/2], undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence and Order Slips-D, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence and Order Slips-E, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence and Order Slips-F, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence and Order Slips-G, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence and Order Slips-H, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence and Order Slips-I, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence and Order Slips-J, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence and Order Slips-K, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence and Order Slips-L, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence and Order Slips-M, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence and Order Slips-N, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence and Order Slips-O, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence and Order Slips-P, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence and Order Slips-R, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence and Order Slips-S, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Stores Department, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence and Order Slips-T, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence and Order Slips-U, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence and Order Slips-W, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence and Order Slips-W, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Purchase Orders, undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - ABL Correspondence-Miss Boyer's File, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - G.W.U. Correspondence-Miss Boyer's File, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous group few of serie 7600-7900-8000-8200-8300-8600-9000 (9821 one only), undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 8101-8200, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 8801-8900, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 9401-9500, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 9501-9600, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - War Production Board, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Zimmerla Auto Shop, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - K.F. Zimmerla Machine Works, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - J.F. Zimmerman, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Zimmerman Wholesale, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - "Z" Miscellaneous, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Merchandise Order Book-Mr. Edw. J. Davis No. 2 [1/3], undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Merchandise Order Book-Mr. E. J. Davis No. 2 [2/3], undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Merchandise Order Book-Mr. Edward Davis No. 2 [3/3], undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Merchandise Order Book-Mrs. M. Amanda Kershner (Formerl E.F.D.) No. 2, undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Merchandise Order Book-Dr. Goff No. 3 [1/2], undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Merchandise Order Book-Dr. Goff No. 3 [2/2], undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Merchandise Order Book-Dr. B.D. Evera No. 5, undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Merchandise Order Book-Mr. Africano No. 6 [1/2], undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Merchandise Order Book-Mr. Africano No. 6 [2/2], undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Merchandise Order Book-Dr. Kossiakoff No. 9, undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Merchandise Order Book-Dr. Osborne No. 11 [1/2], undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Merchandise Order Book-Dr. Osborne No. 11 [2/2], undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Merchandise Order Book-Mr. Donald L. Brasted No. 12, undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Merchandise Order Book-Dr. Gibson-Mr. Burns No. 13 [1/2], undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Merchandise Order Book-Dr. Gibson-Mr. Burns No. 13 [2/2], undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Merchandise Order Book-Mr. Ruppolt No. 16, undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Merchandise Order Book-R. Burkett No. 20 [1/2], undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Merchandise Order Book-Mr. R. Burkett No. 20 [2/2], undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Merchandise Order Book-F.N. Boyer Stock Items an "Emergency" No. 21 [1/3], undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Merchandise Order Book-F.N. Boyer Stock Items an "Emergency" No. 21 [2/3], undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Merchandise Order Book-F.N. Boyer Stock Items an "Emergency" No. 21 [3/3], undated (Box 7, Folder 34)